[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Sai Jinyin,
a woman in the con business like you,
why would you sell your own daughter?
Sir,
what are you talking about?
Kids
don't come cheap.
Food and daily necessities—
every single thing costs money.
She is...
She's your own flesh and blood.
Of course, she is.
Sir,
just look at the two of us.
These eyes, these eyebrows, and this little nose.
This little girl
is the spitting image of me.
Look how young she is.
She's perfect.
You smudged it again.
Hold still.
You little brat, stop right there!
Stop!
I said stop!
Why won't you listen?
I asked why you wouldn't listen!
Is this how it's going to be every day?
Is it?
I told you to listen!
Run!
Let's see you run now!
Let's see where you can run to!
I'll break your legs!
[A Prophet]
[Episode 16]
I left the mortal world to practice physiognomy.
Everything in the mortal world is already in the past.
Thunder may strike, and fire may burn, but the wind cannot be driven away.
Life after life, I belong to the physiognomy sect.
Once you light this incense,
you are members of the Tianxiang Sect.
Now that you've entered the sect,
I have a word for you.
Every single one of us in Yuehaitang
is
a capable woman outside.
We owe all our blessings today
to the grandmaster.
-Thank you, Grandmaster. -Thank you, Grandmaster.
Why do you join the Tianxiang Sect?
I couldn't bear a child
for my husband's family.
So my husband threw me out.
My own family despised my poverty
and refused to take me back.
I truly had nowhere else to go.
Senior,
let her follow me.
My parents passed away when I was young,
and my relatives weren't wealthy.
I wanted to find work in the city,
but no one would take me.
It wasn't until I came to the Tianxiang Sect
that I finally had a full meal.
I just wanted a bite to eat.
If you're asked
to kill someone for a full meal,
will you do it?
Follow me.
As long as you are obedient,
I won't make things difficult for you.
What about you?
I...
I didn't want to study,
so I ran away from home.
If you can't even bear the hardship of studying,
this place isn't for you.
Leave now.
Wait.
They are the Sect Master's people?
Senior,
I've checked the girls' backgrounds.
There are no issues.
Sect Master gave special instructions.
The girls are still useful.
They must stay at the branch.
Then...
let them all stay.
A state has its laws,
and a family has its rules.
From now on,
the Tianxiang Sect
is your home now.
This is a reward from the grandmaster.
-Thank you, Grandmaster. -Thank you, Grandmaster.
Are you asking about your love life, Miss?
Who looks for romance nowadays?
I'm here for my financial fortune.
You are destined
for great wealth.
As the saying goes, heaven is vigorous.
You just need to strive constantly and work hard.
By autumn,
a great fortune will fall from the sky.
Autumn?
I can't wait that long.
Just give me a straight answer.
I'm going to the casino tonight.
Any chance of winning?
Miss, your birth element is Wood.
You have Indirect Wealth in your chart.
You only need a man of the Water element
to stir the energy, and wealth will follow naturally.
What does a Water-element man look like?
Tender or slightly tipsy?
Is he like the guy behind you?
Do you know how many people
envy you for having such a father?
Look here, look here!
Wang Jiaxian!
Why are you here?
Jiaxian,
why are you here?
The last time I saw you
was at your wedding.
That girl was so nice.
This place is boring.
Let's go somewhere else.
I want to have a drink with this girl.
Why did you bring me here?
I was going to ask you the same thing.
Why are you here?
I'm here to meet the mob.
I just met a boss upstairs.
He is...
the Master Swindler.
Why were you looking for him?
I want to take down...
that jerk producer, Tang Yushan.
I want to avenge Manzhi.
Poor Manzhi.
You know what?
Tell me about it first.
What did this guy do to you?
He ruined Ms. He's reputation.
Ms. He died for no reason.
It must be that guy Tang.
Did the police investigate?
They did.
Suicide or homicide?
Suicide.
He agreed?
He asked me for 100 gold bars.
Do I look like a gold bar to you?
100 gold bars for a life.
No.
I don't want his life.
But I want him to apologize.
I want him to kneel.
I want him to repent.
I want to stop him from publishing that book.
Ms. He is already gone.
He wants to publish a book now.
He wants to spread rumors about Ms. He.
He wants to make money off the dead!
He's an animal.
Deal.
I'll help you with this.
For free.
Really?
By the way,
what do you do now?
I'll tell you
everything later.
But you have to promise me one thing first.
As long as you can help me,
I'll do anything.
Words can't express my gratitude.
Jiaxian.
Just one thing.
From now on,
don't call me Wang Jiaxian anymore.
Remember,
call me Shangguan Chengming.
And we've never met before.
Got it?
Shang...
You changed your name?
Why?
So we can get this done for free.
And so you don't mess with that mob boss.
It's easier to invite trouble than to get rid of it,
you know?
Alright,
then it's settled.
Is it?
The mob is here.
It is.
Take care.
It's settled.
I won't see you out.
What do you mean?
It's the prey Master Liu has his eyes on.
Mr. Fan,
a minute ago,
Mr. Yang closed this deal
with me.
You dared to poach clients from your own peers?
You are mistaken, Mr. Fan.
Nowadays,
we believe in fair competition.
You asked for too much
and scared the client away.
Who can you blame for that?
Besides, the decision lies with the buyer,
not the seller.
Don't you even understand this simple logic?
Master.
Shangguan Chengming definitely knows that Yang guy.
He has a guilty conscience.
Those 2 little foxes
dared to play tricks on me.
Wait until they show their true colors.
Understood.
Mom,
keep this money.
Your chronic chest pain
flares up easily in cold weather.
I have asked Manager Liu at the pharmacy
to have the medicine boiled
and brought to you every week from now on.
You must remember to take your medicine on time.
Put aside the tailor shop work
for now.
Don't take on night work, either.
From now on, I'll send the money over
at the end of every month.
Once I'm settled down there,
I'll bring you over.
You're getting older,
yet I can't be by your side to take care of you.
Ms. He was such a great actress.
How did she end up with a jerk like Tang Yushan?
Can also make something of yourself.
You're her fan, aren't you?
Want to get justice for your idol?
I just hope you live well.
You must stay well.
Mom,
take care of yourself.
Tang Yushan used to be a punk.
After latching onto Ms. He,
he suddenly became a producer.
Now that Ms. He is gone,
he still wants to exploit her
by publishing a book.
Didn't I tell you
to mind your own business?
It's not good for you
to offend someone like him.
But I can't just
stand by and watch him profit off her suffering.
Do you really have to do this?
Yang Xiaozhong came to me.
He attended our wedding.
I was afraid that if I didn't help him,
my identity would be exposed.
If you had wanted to silence him,
you should have just killed him.
I'm not joking with you.
Do I look like I'm joking?
Yang Xiaozhong has seen you and me.
Have you ever thought about
what will happen if the sect finds out?
What if Sect Master
finds out?
Don't you think Ms. He is pitiful?
There are plenty of pitiful people
in this world.
Are you going to save them all?
We can barely save ourselves.
Master Swindler is still keeping an eye on you.
If something really happens to you,
who will save you?
I know the rules.
Hiring the Fifth Batou costs money.
I have 2 gold bars in my pocket right now.
My fee for running a con
has always been 3 gold bars.
I'll go borrow one right now.
I won't owe you.
Come back to me
when you have enough money.
Why have you been following me?
Manzhi,
I finally found you.
Bro,
won't we get karma
for doing this?
A kind word moves a man;
a single incense offering moves a ghost.
If Ms. He's spirit is in heaven,
she will understand us.
True.
Wait.
Did you light the incense before opening the coffin?
I did.
Fill in a bit more here.
Here.
Fifth Batou, why are you here?
It's useless for you to do this.
You know what I'm going to do?
People like Tang Yushan
don't buy this at all.
Speak.
Hello?
Mr. Tang,
it's Zhong.
Speak.
Something terrible happened.
Manzhi...
He Manzhi...
I saw her.
If you're possessed,
go pray at a temple, okay?
Don't call me.
No,
there was a rainstorm yesterday, right?
I think I saw her ghost.
I felt uneasy after waking up today,
so I went to the cemetery to check.
The thunder yesterday
broke the tomb.
The tomb was completely open,
and the coffin was exposed.
The coffin was exposed?
You saw it with your own eyes?
The coffin was full of hair,
jet-black hair.
Mr. Tang, she has a grievance.
Then please
put her coffin back in the grave.
Then seal the tomb shut.
While you're at it,
send a bouquet of flowers to Manzhi for me.
Tell her
I will always love her,
always.
It didn't work.
I said all that,
but he still wouldn't go to her grave to take a look.
What did I say?
A jerk like him
has no sense of shame.
He doesn't revere ghosts or gods.
He only cares about himself.
Not afraid of ghosts?
That's because he hasn't seen one.
Lin Xiangyu,
stop messing around.
I won't sign
such an unreasonable agreement.
Don't forget who made you famous!
I've had a hard life since I was a kid.
Mr. Tang,
I've read the first half of your manuscript.
It's absolutely brilliant.
But for the second half, could you give us
something more sensational?
Chief Editor Zheng,
I'm sorry.
I really don't know how to keep writing.
Because whenever I pick up my pen,
I think of her.
I think of her the moment I pick up my pen.
Plus, the recent royalty issues
are driving me crazy.
I just can't write anymore. I'm sorry.
Mr. Tang.
Regarding the publishing rights,
we are willing to pay 50%
above the market price.
50%?
Chief Editor Zheng,
please take back what you just said, okay?
Fuxiang Publishing House offered
twice what you're paying.
Do you know why I turned them down?
The Story of My Past with He Manzhi.
What price can be put on these words?
Can this ever be measured in money?
I think the quote is just a formality.
It represents
respect for Manzhi.
Please say no more.
I feel this is an insult to art,
an insult to me,
and an insult to my wife, okay?
Mr. Tang,
I will absolutely show my utmost sincerity.
It's just that
I need to discuss this with our president again.
Easy.
My friend.
You are still young.
There are some things you don't see clearly.
Have you ever thought about
how much wealth it could create
if you convince the president
to buy up the rights to this sure-to-become-hit novel—
the film production rights,
and even the sequel film rights,
all bundled together,
at a very reasonable price?
And if this succeeds,
do you think
I'd forget my friends?
What is this?
Can you guys do anything right?
I will pay you back every single penny.
But you won't take away
even a shred of my dignity.
Who is it?
Stop messing around.
♪ Night rain taps the window, dampening the silk canopy ♪
♪ The face in the mirror still wears its old look ♪
♪ I trace an eyebrow to hide the tear in my eye ♪
Who's there?
♪ My love, tell me if I'm cold or burning hot ♪
I see you!
♪ Rouge is as red as blood plasma ♪
♪ Stained on lips, yet sealed deep in your heart ♪
♪ This red thread loops round my neck ♪
♪ It tightens more; even broken, our bond endures ♪
♪ We crazily love each other ♪
♪ We're a pair in this life ♪
♪ Lying in one bed; sharing one coffin when dead ♪
♪ Turn to ash and dust, mixed as one instead ♪
♪ Don't look back or panic ♪
♪ Right here, by your side ♪
♪ Press to your back and breathe your scent ♪
Won't sleep, huh?
♪ With cold long nails, I loose your robe ♪
Wanna die?
Close it!
I said close...
♪ We crazily love each other ♪
♪ Through every life, we remain as a pair ♪
♪ You can't flee, and I can't leave ♪
♪ I must speak to you about this bitter grudge ♪
[Die]
♪ We crazily love each other ♪
♪ We're a pair in this life ♪
♪ Lying in one bed; sharing one coffin when dead ♪
♪ Turn to ash and dust, mixed as one instead ♪
♪ Don't look back or panic ♪
♪ Right here, by your side ♪
♪ Press to your back and breathe your scent ♪
♪ With cold long nails, I loose your robe ♪
♪ We crazily love each other ♪
♪ Through every life, we remain as a pair ♪
♪ You can't flee, and I can't leave ♪
♪ I must speak to you about this bitter grudge ♪
Yushan.
Don't you miss me?
Then why did you
want to kill me?
So easily frightened.
Thank you,
♪ Rouge is as red as blood plasma ♪
Fourth Batou.
♪ Stained on lips, yet sealed deep in your heart ♪
♪ This red thread loops round my neck ♪
I heard you never set traps.
♪ It tightens more; even broken, our bond endures ♪
Why help me?
Who said I never set traps?
Who wouldn't want to enforce justice on behalf of Heaven?
♪ You can't flee, and I can't leave ♪
That's also why Sect Master
♪ I must speak to you about this bitter grudge ♪
let me join the Tianxiang Sect back then.
You're quite naive.
You joined the Tianxiang Sect
just to enforce justice.
For so many years,
all the people in the sect have thought about is how to harm others
and swindle money.
You are different from them.
Get closer.
Closer.
Master Chang.
I'm good here.
If you're too far,
the victim won't feel it.
When I opened the coffin for the autopsy just now,
I noticed signs of a zombie transformation.
But don't be afraid.
I've set up a formation.
It's safe.
Once I perform a ritual,
you can rest easy.
The victim's resentment should dissipate.
♪ He Manzhi bears unjust grief ♪
Master!
♪ Wed Tang Yushan by wrong fate ♪
♪ Tang Yushan, a wolfish spouse ♪
♪ Took her life and severed all kin ties ♪
I can't do this job!
♪ Yin and mortal realms hold this trial ♪
My cultivation isn't strong enough
to suppress it!
But you have to save me.
♪ My husband Tang Yushan is a beast ♪
You have to save me.
How about I invite my mentor
to take a look?
Go invite him right now.
♪ He stole my life away ♪
Okay.
Let's go.
♪ Redress He Manzhi's unjust wrongs ♪
Mr. Tang, please be patient.
My mentor will definitely have a way.
Performing this ritual
will probably exhaust all my cultivation.
Mentor, if it consumes so much of your cultivation,
we might as well not do this ritual.
Please, no!
Mentor.
No.
Master.
I heard you were coming.
Look, I've spent my money
setting up the formation again.
You have to do this.
Money is not an issue.
You must help me.
The sage puts himself last and rises to the fore;
he sets himself aside, and his life endures.
It means putting others before oneself.
I'll help you with this.
Break!
Break the ground.
Open the coffin.
Master.
Hair.
Just as I expected.
Ms. He's resentment has turned into pus and blood.
Soon, it will gather into a soul
and become a vengeful spirit.
Mr. Tang, you found me just in time.
But
I'll need you for the next step.
Me?
You can't leave, Mr. Tang!
Only a close relative
can bring Ms. He's soul back to her body.
Mr. Tang,
go hold her hand now.
No matter what happens, don't let go.
I can't hold it!
Mr. Tang, we can't give up halfway!
Mr. Tang!
Yushan.
Help!
Ms. He's soul has returned.
Mr. Tang, if you have anything to say to her,
say it now.
I have nothing to say to her.
What should I say?
Say whatever will put her at ease.
But remember, you must tell the truth.
Manzhi.
Stop thinking about me.
I'm doing fine here.
Hurry up and reincarnate.
Let's be husband and wife again in the next life!
Why did you kill me?
Why?
I...
I told you to tell the truth.
Is there something else you haven't said?
Nothing.
Tang Yushan,
tell me now.
Why on earth did you kill me?
I'll tell you.
Master.
Let us have a private talk.
Give me some space, okay?
Mentor.
Don't go too far!
Don't worry.
Don't go any further!
You two just stay there!
Right there!
Go ahead and speak!
Manzhi,
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it back then.
Reincarnate well.
I'll repay you...
in my next life.
I'll be your beast of burden
in my next life. Please let me go.
What are these people doing?
They don't seem to be our guys.
Where is Yang Xiaozhong?
Him?
Yang Xiaozhong always talked about exposing this animal.
Do you think he arranged for these people?
Oh no.
Are you even human?
Do you have any humanity?
You wouldn't let He Manzhi go
when she was alive!
Now that she's dead, you still won't let her rest in peace, will you?
Fine then.
Don't you want to take pictures?
Come on!
Take pictures of me!
Take all the pictures you want!
Manzhi!
I'm so sorry for you!
I didn't give you a good life
when you were alive.
And I can't even let you rest in peace after you're dead,
Manzhi!
Mr. Tang, there's no need for this.
I hear you've recently
been writing a biography of Ms. He.
Ms. He's fans have been
watching this book closely.
When do you plan to publish it?
Rumor has it that due to gambling,
your financial situation has been poor.
Are you facing great difficulties
with the publishing funds?
I don't care
if everyone slanders me.
But
all of you, remember this.
I will definitely
publish this book.
I'll publish it
even if I have to sell
everything I own!
There are so many things in this book
that I want to say to Manzhi.
She can't hear them anymore.
Do you have any thoughts of adapting it into a movie?
Of course, I do!
Listen up!
Not only will I adapt this book into a movie,
but I'll also make the movie
become
a milestone in Chinese film history!
He Manzhi,
I love you!
I will definitely make this movie well
and finish it for you!
Yang Xiaozhong meant well but did a bad thing,
paving the way for this beast.
Here is...
the gold bar I owed you.
You gave up?
I couldn't just beat that bastard to death.
I saw He Manzhi's mother
after the movie that day.
She was delirious
and mistook me for He Manzhi.
The old lady still doesn't believe
her daughter is dead.
Tell me,
is it worth it
to seek justice for a dead person?
Maybe...
for some of the living,
it's the only thing worth doing.
These 3 gold bars are the payment you gave me.
We're even.
Now,
I'm giving them to you
to hire you to work for me.
I'll take
this deal.
[In the next episode]
Are you filming a movie?
Who should I act with?
He Manzhi.
He Man...
He Manzhi?
Okay.
Attention, all departments.
Rolling.
Ah.
Look how beautiful I am in the mirror.
But...
I'm sorry, Director.
Do we have to film this movie?
We must do it.
I want everyone to witness
He Manzhi's return.
I'll make this movie...
You want me to summon souls?
A smash hit.
Necklace.
Soul seizure.
Once she wears that necklace,
Manyu
will be possessed.
But I know
this is not me.